- This is Ranma...
- Hi.
...of the Saotome School
of Anything Goes Martial Arts.
- This is Akane of the Tendo Dojo.
- Uh... Eh? What? Huh?
These two were put into
an arranged betrothal by their parents.
You don't get a say in what I do.
But Ranma has a bit of a problem.
- Whenever he's splashed with cold water...
- Ah!
...he transforms into a girl.
RANMA1/2
DARLING CHARLOTTE
There!
Akane,
can we take a little break?
We were wanting to get
something warm to eat.
Okay.
There's a skating club?
Yeah, you should join.
I'm sure they'll be happy to make you
a full member right away.
I'm still trying to figure out
what I want to do.
A lot of people have been asking me
to help with their club.
Huh?
- Hmm? Oh, no.
- Huh?
I think I might have left P-chan
on the ice.
What is a P-chan?
Is that her little black pig?
Charlotte.
You're a Charlotte.
I'm totally taking you home with me.
Mm-hmm. Come on, Charlotte.
You're so cute!
Okay, break it down for me again.
Why do you think I'm related to this girl?
Don't play dumb with us, Ranma.
You really expect us
to believe you're not?
She introduced herself
with the name Ranma Saotome.
And she has the same pigtail as you.
- And she's a strong martial artist.
- I bet she's your cousin or sister.
Whoever she is,
you need to introduce us!
Hmm. Don't know her, but...
...sounds pretty dumb.
Hey! Are you running away from us?
And all of this
after having the nerve to deflower Akane?
I did what to who now?
Please! Will you at least
let us have dibs on this one?
You shouldn't be hogging the fun
to yourself!
Why do you idiots keep insisting that
I want an unsexy little tomboy like Akane?
- Ranma!
- Huh?
Huh? Whoa, w-what are you doing?
You wanna fight?
Come on.
You don't have to start crying, you know?
And besides, it doesn't matter...
...how unsexy you are,
'cause it's not like, uh...
P-chan is missing!
It's not like I really care...
Hmm?
P-chan disappeared
from the skating rink earlier.
He was kidnapped!
There are people who witnessed it.
Hey, welcome!
I wish I could help you, but...
Hmm?
Remind me what this pig looked like again.
Could you be serious for once?
I mean, what am I seeing over there?
It's P-chan!
Back off! What do you think you're doing?
You leave me
and my piggy, Charlotte, alone.
Say what? I'm positive that's my P-chan.
And if I say that it's Charlotte,
then it's Charlotte.
CHARLOTTE - P-CHAN
- No, that's mine.
- Hey, welcome!
- I want it. Give it back.
- Hmm?
- This yours?
- Yes, he is.
Oh!
I hope you forgive my partner.
Wow, oh, wow, that guy's really hot.
No harm done. Thank you.
You're such a big...
She tends to have a habit of taking
cute things that don't belong to her.
Once she gets locked in on something,
it'll often go home with her
right on the spot.
Dude, isn't that, like, a crime?
Give me!
Gimme! Give me!
Would you stop doing that,
you stupid girl!
Oh, no. You're, like, so mean.
Hmm?
I really wanna face off with you.
So, what? Are you saying you want a fight?
Please! I'm not an animal.
We'll face off in pair skating.
You want to skate?
Yes, and if I win, I'm totally demanding
that you give back Charlotte.
- Now I remember.
- Hmm?
I know them. I kept thinking
they looked familiar.
Those two are the golden pair of Freestyle
Skating from Kolkhoz High School.
I'm Azusa Shiratori. Hi.
Huh. I'm Mikado Sanzenin.
Are you gonna
place an order or not?
Akane, you don't want to be
in a skating match against them.
Their skills are
way beyond ordinary students'.
You know I don't care about that.
If you're a smart girl,
you'll surrender while you still can.
I knew
that whole innocent thing was an act.
Wait for me, Charlotte. I'll be getting
your room ready in the meantime.
Don't worry about her, P-chan.
I promise I'm not gonna lose.
Sounds pretty dumb.
Miss, I'm sorry.
- My partner gets herself in trouble.
- Huh?
I can make it up to you, easily.
Huh?
Ranma, you...
It's an unorthodox white glove,
but I'll accept your challenge.
We'll face off in one week.
Kolkhoz High School will serve
as the venue.
Aw! I can't believe how cute that is!
I want it! Give it!
- The challenge will be pair skating. Deal?
- Give it to me!
- Yeah, whatever.
- Give me François!
François! Give it to me!
Give me François!
You are absolutely ruining all of
my dramatic tension, you idiotic girl!
This is mine now. Yay.
When the hell you gonna order something?
- Why do you have to be like this?
- Let's go home.
- Can't you be normal for once?
- François.
Let me make something clear.
That wasn't me getting jealous back there.
I'm just not a fan of those player-types
getting away with that kinda crap.
Well, it was still unnecessary.
You know what?
You should thank me for helping you out...
Oh.
Hmm. Hang on.
Do you like that kinda guy?
You're so dumb.
If that fish cake were
a fraction of a second slower,
I think you probably would have seen
me crack his chin open.
If you weren't unsexy before,
you are now.
Maybe I'll bother with all that
stuff when I find someone worth liking.
You're having a pair skate
showdown and P-chan is the prize?
So, are you two gonna pair up?
You know that means
you'll have to be all synced-up, right?
In your own way, I suppose
you two are always in harmony.
You really think so?
I gotta tell you, I don't really care...
...what happens to the pig.
Allow me to be the one to take the ice.
Akane, I'd be honored to skate with you.
I'm curious. Did somebody already tell you
about the skating match, Charlotte?
Who do you think
you're calling Charlotte?
Regardless of how good you are at this,
I was the one who issued the challenge.
Then maybe now's the time
for our own skating battle.
All right!
Instead of that, maybe we should try
practicing how to stand first?
Look at you.
What's with the posture?
Shut your face!
How are you supposed to participate in a
skating competition when you can't skate?
It's not like I had a choice.
All right, get a grip.
I thought you were a man.
Yeah, but right now, I'm a girl.
Why go through the hassle
of splashing yourself with cold water
before coming out here?
Yeah, I mean, it's not very cool
if a man doesn't know how to skate.
I doubt the uncoolness factor has
much to do with being a boy or a girl.
Wait, where did P-chan go?
Whoops, so sorry about that.
Azusa Shiratori.
I know you did that on purpose.
I'd never! Also, it seems your partner is
giving you enough things to worry about.
Huh?
Somebody help! Help me!
Please, somebody help!
Hello, there. Are you all right?
Uh, you're that Mikado Sanzenin guy.
Huh? Have we happened to meet before?
How very odd.
Yes, I would be surprised.
I don't believe I'd ever forget
a pretty face like yours.
You can have fun picking up
all the girls you want later.
It's time for the 100-man kumite now.
You're doing that? Really?
Is that part of your training routine?
Huh?
You ladies should step back for a bit.
I would never want for you to get hurt.
Come at us.
Let the hundred-man kumite begin!
Wow! Look at them go.
We're finished now.
In nine seconds flat.
They really are the golden pair
of the Freestyle Skating Martial Team.
The Martial Team, huh?
T-That means we'll be using
martial skating to face off!
I can win. I can win anything
that has the name "martial" in it!
Of course you can. But I'm pretty sure
you need to learn how to skate first.
- Look. There's a pig!
- Aw!
Hang on, little guy.
There's P-chan.
Hello, Charlotte!
Hmph.
Hey, Akane! Whoa!
Here, P-chan.
Let sweet Azusa spoil you
with a little present.
That's just so cute!
Geez. Ugh, you're horrible.
Putting a collar on him.
CHARLOTTE
What-what is this?
I'm taking this thing off you right now.
That's not going to work.
Unfortunately, I locked the clasp.
So if you want me to take the collar off,
then you'll have to defeat me
in our showdown later.
It's not gonna matter
how good the golden pair is
because when Ranma and I
team up together--
Get over here, stupid!
I-I'm falling over!
I can't stand up anymore!
Hurry up and help me--
I'm happy to give you
private skating lessons.
I didn't ask for your help.
Let go of me, prick!
Well, I'm sorry to hear that.
But if that's the case...
...let me take a parting gift
for saving you.
Ooh!
Oh. Wait, Miss...
Ranma...
What a pure heart she has,
for her to sob so violently like that.
I would cry too if it was you kissing me.
PUBLIC BATH
So gross. How dare that ass
put his hands on me like that?
And he did it in front of Akane,
of all people!
Mmm...
- I'll never forgive him!
- Whoa!
Ah! Just a tiny kiss
and she broke down with tears of joy.
Lock me up for crimes of the heart.
Sanzenin!
You and I are gonna fight right now.
But don't think you have a chance
of surviving this.
Uh... Ranma?
Ah, the guy from earlier.
You just show up
out of nowhere, don't you?
I'm infuriated.
This is the first time I've felt rage
like this in my life!
I don't quite know what it is
that you're so angry about,
but for inflicting damage to this
sacred space, your blood will spill here.
I was thinking the same thing.
For all the humiliation
you've put me through...
...I'll make you pay!
Oh, wow.
His head just broke through the ice.
How pathetic.
I suppose that's the end of it for you.
I was resistant to using this technique
when facing such an obvious amateur.
Huh? I know that stance.
That's his ultimate technique,
Dance of Death!
Dance of Death? That doesn't sound good.
This looks bad. No one has
ever escaped his spin attack before.
Anyone caught in Sanzenin's vortex is left
writhing in agony, like they're dancing.
I mean, literally,
this is the Dance of Death!
Whoa. Perfection.
Ranma, can you stand?
Hang on.
How's he still able to move around like
that after getting hit by that technique?
Shall we call it a draw?
Ranma was the winner.
Huh?
Hmm.
Deary me. I think he passed out.
- Huh?
- Eh?
Let's draw on his face!
Hey, I wanna draw something.
Heck, yeah. Me too.
TENDO DOJO
I mean, really,
you're so immature.
Was it necessary to hit him
more than 500 times to beat him?
I don't wanna hear it.
He deserved a heck of a lot
worse than that
after he went and slobbered
all over my face.
Is it just me
or are you kinda acting fussy?
So, what exactly did he do to you?
Nothing. He did nothing.
You were looking real lame
out there, Ranma.
Oh, Ryoga.
I never would've gotten myself
into a situation like that to begin with.
Yeah, well, if I hadn't been wearing those
skates, it would've been a lot easier--
You think you could've
somehow avoided the kiss?
Ah, got it. So someone tried
to kiss Ranma earlier today?
Who were you macking on?
Well, I guess the one positive thing
you can take from this
is that it came from a very sexy man.
It was a man?
There's no reason
for you to be ashamed about that.
I guess it'd be a little tragic
if it was a first kiss or something.
Oh, no, I'm sure there's no way
that could be the case, right, Ranma?
Damn it. Why does everybody think
it's okay to make fun of me?
No one understands how I feel.
Your back is wide open.
Why's your guard down?
You're not still sulking, are you?
Just laugh at me
if you think it's so funny.
Oh, come on, it's not that funny.
Wait. That wasn't
actually your first kiss, was it?
Hmm?
No, and it's
none of your business.
You're right.
I'll stop being so nosy then.
You know what I was thinking though?
Ow.
You probably haven't trained hard enough
if that guy was able to plant
a big, old smooch on you like that.
You're always going around
talking a big game,
but then you tend to let your guard down.
Looks like you've got no room to talk.
Uh...
Uh, wait,
don't get the wrong idea.
I wasn't going to swoop in
and kiss you like that guy or anything.
Yeah, okay. I know that.
You don't have the guts
to do something like that anyway.
Well, if you keep talking
like that, I'm gonna do it!
I'd be very interested
to see if you actually can.
Fine. Here I go.
But you gotta close your eyes.
Hmm? Hmm.
Hmm.
I mean, uh, I don't know...
Should we do this?
I-Is it a good idea?
It'd be better to do this
with someone you like.
Wouldn't it?
Oh, yeah.
I must not be good enough for you.
- You know that's not what I was saying!
- Hmm?
'Cause I... I don't wanna do it
if it's a big deal.
You know?
Uh-huh.
Hmm?
Hurry up and decide
if you're gonna do this already.
Some of us have stuff to get done!
They're late bloomers.
Damn you, Ranma Saotome.
The day we face off will be
the last one you ever live through!